http://www.apeal.org/privacy-centre/

Privacy Centre
APEAL is committed to protecting privacy of personal data. Our Privacy Centre provides information on how we collect, store and process personal data and allows visitors to exercise their rights in line with the EU’s General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR).
Find out more on how we collect and process personal data
Cookies Policy
You can consult our cookies policy and a full list of cookies used on this website.
COOKIES POLICY
Privacy Policy
You can read our privacy policy that outlines how we collect, process and store data.
PRIVACY POLICY
TERMS OF USE
Terms of use outline a range of policies and disclaimers specific to this site.
TERMS OF USE
Your Rights
The EU’s General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) grants you specific rights to find out more on the personal data we have, to be deleted from our databases, to correct data and to limit the processing of your personal data.
Right to information
Ask us if we hold any of your personal data and how it is processed and the rationale for the data processing.
REQUEST INFORMATION
Right to access
Request a copy of the personal data we have in our database.
REQUEST INFORMATION
Right to rectification
If you think the personal data we have on record is not up to date or incorrect, you can ask us to correct it.
REQUEST RECTIFCATION
Right to withdraw consent
If you would like to withdraw a previously given consent to store your personal data or send you information you can withdraw that consent.
WITHDRAW CONSENT
Right to object
If you would like us to keep your personal data on record but no longer process this data (e.g. send you newsletters), please be specific as to what type of processing you object to.
SEND A REQUEST
Right to object to automated processing
We do not process personal data automatically.
Right of Erasure
If you would like to be deleted from our database as far as it is in line with other applicable laws you click on the button below.
SEND REQUEST
Right for data portability
If you would like your personal data to be transferred to another organisation, we will provide your data in a machine readable format.
SEND REQUEST
Questions?
If anything is unclear, please contact us
IMPORTANT
For all requests, please include your full name and e-mail address which will help us in their handling.
If you have a complaint about our use of your information, you can contact the Belgian Privacy Commission.
Belgian Privacy Commission
Drukpersstraat 35, 1000 Brussels
Tel +32 (0)2 274 48 00
commission@privacycommission.be
This website uses cookies to improve user experience. Read about how we use cookies and how you can control them by clicking “Change Cookie Settings” or accept cookies by clicking “Accept Cookies”.
Accept Cookies
Read more
Change Cookie Settings
Cookie Box Settings
Cookie Box Settings
Decide which cookies you want to allow.
You can change cookie setting at any time. However, this can result in some functions no longer being available.
Learn more about the cookies we use.
You can opt in by clicking on the cookie types below:
Block all
Essentials
Functionality
Analytics
Advertising
This website will:
Essential: Remember your cookie permission settingEssential: Allow session cookiesEssential: Gather information you input into a contact forms, newsletter and other forms across all pagesEssential: Authenticate that you are logged into your user account
This website won
Functionality: Remember social media settingsFunctionality: Remember selected region and countryFunctionality: Remember language version you selectedFunctionality: Identify device you are usingAnalytics: Keep track of your visited pagesAnalytics: Keep track about your location and region based on your IP addressAnalytics: Keep track on the time spent on each pageAnalytics: Identify device you are usingAdvertising: Allow you to connect to social sitesAdvertising: Gather personally identifiable informationRemember your login details
This website will:
Essential: Remember your cookie permission settingEssential: Allow session cookiesEssential: Gather information you input into a contact forms, newsletter and other forms across all pagesEssential: Authenticate that you are logged into your user accountFunctionality: Remember social media settingsFunctionality: Remember selected region and countryFunctionality: Remember language version you selectedFunctionality: Identify device you are using
This website won
Analytics: Keep track of your visited pagesAnalytics: Keep track about your location and region based on your IP addressAnalytics: Keep track on the time spent on each pageAnalytics: Identify device you are usingAdvertising: Allow you to connect to social sitesRemember your login detailsAdvertising: Gather personally identifiable information
This website will:
Essential: Remember your cookie permission settingEssential: Allow session cookiesEssential: Gather information you input into a contact forms, newsletter and other forms across all pagesEssential: Authenticate that you are logged into your user accountFunctionality: Remember social media settingsFunctionality: Remember selected region and countryFunctionality: Remember language version you selectedFunctionality: Identify device you are usingAnalytics: Keep track of your visited pagesAnalytics: Keep track about your location and region based on your IP addressAnalytics: Keep track on the time spent on each pageAnalytics: Identify device you are using
This website won
Advertising: Allow you to connect to social sitesAdvertising: Gather personally identifiable informationRemember your login details
This website will:
Essential: Remember your cookie permission settingEssential: Allow session cookiesEssential: Gather information you input into a contact forms, newsletter and other forms across all pagesEssential: Authenticate that you are logged into your user accountFunctionality: Remember social media settingsFunctionality: Remember selected region and countryFunctionality: Remember language version you selectedFunctionality: Identify device you are usingAnalytics: Keep track of your visited pagesAnalytics: Keep track about your location and region based on your IP addressAnalytics: Keep track on the time spent on each pageAnalytics: Identify device you are usingAdvertising: Allow you to connect to social sitesAdvertising: Gather personally identifiable information
This website won
Remember your login details
Save & Close
X
Subscribe now to our Steel for Packaging Update Newsletter (in English or Spanish)
Subscribe
